ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/168
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- United Nations Economic & Social Council, Draft Report Wholesale Price Statistics; Draft Report on Statistics of Underdeveloped Countries, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Item 30: How to get those 14,000,000 new homes we need in the Sixties - without inflation, Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Item 31: Women's Garment Industry vs. Others, Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
- United Nations Economic & Social Council, Draft Report Wholesale Price Statistics; Draft Report on Statistics of Underdeveloped Countries, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Review of Price in Reases - prospective or actual in key economic sectors, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: The Function of Management in Achieving Sound Labor Relations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    By Lazare Teper. July 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Memo to Congress: a positive program for America, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: Annual Indexes of Payrolls, U.S., Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Annual Indexes of Output per Man-Hour and Unit Wage Costs, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: Index of Wholesale Prices, Nondurable Goods, United States (1947-49=1000), Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: Annual Indexes of Industrial Production, U.S. 1947-49=100, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 8: Annual Indexes of Average Hourly Earnings, U.S. 1947-49=100, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 9: Annual Indexes of Man-Hours, U.S. 1947-49=100, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 10: Average Hourly Earnings, United States, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    1947-1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Index of Wholesale Prices, All Manufacturing, United States (1947-49=100), Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 12: Index of Wholesale prices, Durable Goods, United States (1947-49=100), Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 13: Occupational Shifts in Manufacturing Employment: Some Implications for Productivity and unit Labor Cost Measurements, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    By Murray Wernick. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Cost Inflation on vs. Demand Inflation: A Useful Distinction?, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    By William G. Bowen. January 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Indexes of Average Hourly Earnings, Output per Manhour, Unit Wage Costs and Wholesale Prices, Manufacturing, United States, 1947-1959, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 16: Indexes of Average Hourly Earnings, Output per Manhour, Unit Wage Costs and Wholesale Prices, Manufacturing, United States, 1947-1959, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 17: Indexes of Average Hourly Earnings, Output per Manhour, Unit Wage Costs and Wholesale prices, Manufacturing, United States, 1947-1959, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 18: Notes in Re. Special Estimates For The Table On Pressure On Costs In Manufacturing Corporations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    February 15, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Indexes of Average Hourly Earnings, Output per Manhour, Unit Wage Costs and Wholesale Prices, Manufacturing, United States, 1951-1958, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    February 17, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Changes In Consumer's Price Index and Wholesale Price Index, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    April 1958 - January 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Pressures on Costs, Manufacturing Corporations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 22: Indexes of Average Hourly Earnings, Output per Manhour, Unit Wage Costs and Wholesale Prices, Manufacturing, United States, 1947 to 1959, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 23: Post world war II period, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 24: Annual Links in A Number of Indicators, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 25: Some of the factors bearing on post 1955 price movements:, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 26: Direction of price movements during recessions, 1836-1938, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 27: Wallis, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    June 29, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Trade Union Policy, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 29: Changes in Wholesale Prices, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 30: Schultze's theses, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 31: Labor Force Participation Rate, Unemployment As Percent of Civilian Labor Force, and Average Duration of Unemployment, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 32: Unemployment, Part-Time Employment, Unemployment As Percent of Civilian Labor Force, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    January 1956 - January 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Draft Report: Wholesale Price Statistics, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 34: Draft Report: Capital Formation Statistics In Under-Developed Countries, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    April 29 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Proyecto De Informe: Estadisticas Sobre Las Empresas, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    April 29, 1960. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 36: Draft Report: Input-Output, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    April 28, 1960. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 37: Amendments to E/CN.3/L.52/Add.6, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
- I.L.G.W.U. to Mr. David Dubinsky, President, Assorted Newspaper Articles on Strikes, 1918-1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Collection of Articles, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Sent to David Dubinsky. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report of the activities of the Association, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    By George M. Price. September 12, 1918. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Knitgoods Workers Voice, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    June 15, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Farewell to Hochman, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: Copy of the Call, and Signers of Call, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    April 20, 1933. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Letter and Draft sent to President and other National Leaders, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    By K. Phillips Morgan. September 21, 1931. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor's Voice on Unemployment, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    By Fannia M. Cohn. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Case No. 108, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    January 15, 1931. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Case No. 104, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Joint Council Knitgoods Working Union, Knitgoods Workers Voice, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Workers of the Bamberger-Reinthal Knitting Mills, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Workers of the Federal Knitting Co. Do Not Be Misled!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Workers of the Friedman Blau Farber, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: Workers of Federal Knitting Mills, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: C.I.O. Chief - John L. Lewis, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 6: Knit Goods Workers The Secret Is Out!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 7: Knitgoods Workers!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 8: Knitgoods Workers Mass Meeting, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    June 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Are You One of the Girls Who Says, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 10: A Great Army of Fine Women!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 11: To All Girls Who Work on Silk or Cotton Underwear, Slips, Petticoats, Kimonos, Negligees, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 12: An Appeal to the Colored Dress-makers, Pressers and Finishers, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 13: Workers on Silk and Cotton Underwear, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 14: Demand Pay fo Decoration Day, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 15: Are Some of You Waiting to Join the Union until Conditions Become so Bad that You are Forced to Strike>, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 16: To the Men and Women Working in the Steam and Wet Wash Laundries, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 17: A Great Army of Fine Women!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 18: Gym Information, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    By Leo Cohen. June 11, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Ladies Underwear Worker, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    August 19, 1933. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Don't Work on Belts!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Item is in Jewish, Italian.
  - Item 21: Letters Sent by the Joint Countil Knitgoods Workers Union, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    June 19, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Appeal, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 23: Only Strong Unions Will Put Life Into the Recovery Act, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 24: Mass-Meeting of all wives of cloakmakers, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Item is in Yiddish.
  - Item 25: Citizens of Cumberland, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 26: Great Victory for the Ladies Garment Workers, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 27: Resolution, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 28: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 29: Notice: Monster Mass Meeting, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 30: Americanizing the Petticoat Industry!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 31: Can the Conditions of the Cincinnati Cloakmakers Be Improved?, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 32: Four Questions., Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 33: To All The Girls: Working at Waists, Dresses, White goods, Corsets and Wrappers, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 34: A Mass Meeting, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 35: Join the General Strike, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 36: To Organized Labor and its Friends, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    March 27, 1912. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: A Call of Duty To All Waist And Dressmakers In Hartford, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 38: Waist Makers of Hartford, Arise!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Item is in Italian; English.
  - Item 39: A Call of Duty!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 40: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 41: Waist Makers of New Haven Arise!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 42: Olvasd! Gondolkozz Es Cselekedj!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Item is in Hungarian.
  - Item 43: A Call of Duty! To All Waist and Dress Makers of Stamford, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 44: Wake up from your Sleep!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 45: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 46: Waist Makers of New Haven Arise!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 47: Merry Christmas and A Happy New Year, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 48: To Organized Labor of Anderson, Indiana!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 49: Merry Christmas and A Happy New Year, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 50: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 51: The Message, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Item is in Yiddish; English; Italian.
  - Item 52: Only Strong Unions Will Put Life Into the Recovery Act, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 53: The Injunction: Police Brutality, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 54: An Important Message!, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
- IWW 1920 Convention, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  May 10-20,1920
  - Item 1: Twelth Convetion: Industrial Workers of the World, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    May 10, 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Third Day: Morning Session, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    May 12, 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Fourth Day: Morning Session, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    May 13, 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Seventh Afternoon Session, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    May 17, 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Eight Day: Morning Session, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    May 18, 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Ninth Day: Morning Session, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    May 19, 1920. Item is in English.
- Labor Chronicle 1932, 1935; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  English and Yiddish
  - Item 1: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Labor Chronicle, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
    September 1935. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Memorandum in the matter of the application of the Temporary Disability Benefits Act to the health and welfare funds of the ILGWU, 1948; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Memorandum in the matter of the application of the Temporary Disability benefits Act to the Health and Welfare Funds of the I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
- New York (State) Commission on Medical Care - ILGWU 40th Anniversary Convention, 1940; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  May 1940
  - Item 1: Drafts for statement of AFL position on New York State Medical Care Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: New York State Commission on Medical Care, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Correspondence between Lemboke and Mitchell, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The New York State Federation of Labor rejects the draft report of the Commission on Medical Care as submitted August 25, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Dewey Board Split Over Medical Care, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    February 16, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Letter to Falk, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    December 4, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Alternative Plans for Medical Insurance, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    August 25, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Memorandum regarding New York State Medical Care Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Memorandum about New York State Medical Care Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Letter to Dr. McLean, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Broadus Mitchell. October 9, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Memorandum about New York State Medical Care Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Chart with Plans, Comprehensive Scheme, Home and Office Care, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Memorandum, Subject: New York State Medical Care Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Copy of Letter to Dr. Basil MacLean, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Leo Price. September 25, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Us Need Service Memo, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Report of Conference on Dental Care for Children, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By U.S. Public Health Service. February 22-23, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Distribution of Families and Sample Consumers by Money Income Level 1942 (Estimated), Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Mayors Committee Estimate of Use of Various Services, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    January 15, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Chart of Proposed N.Y. State Medical Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Distribution of Income, New York City Estimated Percentage Distribution of All Families, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Households in New York City, 1940 Clarrified by number of persons in household, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: AfterAccording to Selected Services, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Distribution of Types of Medical Care, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Handwritten Memo, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Letter to Sheila Helmann, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Leo Price. October 9, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: McFadden Publications: Estimates of Distribution of Income by Familites (1) Estimates as of January 1, 1942, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Distribution of Money Expenditure for Medical Care (White Families), Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Distribution of Types of Medical Cases, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: Distribution of Cases Requiring Nursing Care, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Distribution of Income, New York City: Estimated Percentage Distribution of All Families by Amounts of Annual Income, 1935-36 (1) (Native and Foreign Areas Combined), Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Households in New York City, 1940: Classified by Number of Persons in Household, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Mayor's Committee Estimation of Use of Various Services, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: Attendance According to Selected Services: Union Health Center, 1943, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Selected Medical Service Plans: Costs and Benefits, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: Davis - Handwritten Memo, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Services and Costs for Diseases and Conditions Requiring Diagnosis and Treatment (1) Annual Service Expectancy Rates per 1,000 Persons: Total Costs Based on Adopted Fee Schedules and Costs per Unit of Service, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Basis of Plan - Handwritten Notes, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Handwritten Notes, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Research Department; V.2, V.1 of Exhibits submitted by the ILGWU in the matter of the application of the Temporary Disability Benefits Act to the health and welfare funds of the ILGWU, 1948; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Volume 2: Vol.1 of Exhibits submitted by I.L.G.W.U. in the matter of the application of the Temporary Disability Benafits Act to the health and Welfare funds of the I.L.G.W.Ul., Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
- La ILGWU, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Spanish
  - Item 1: El Sello De La ILGWU Es La Mejor Garantia De La Operaria Y De La Alta Calidad De Su Trabajo, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Tu, La Delegada y la Agente de Negocios, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Todos los Problemas Pueden Resolverse Hablando, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Los Sindicos del Plan Medico en Accion, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Asi Estafan a Trabajadores No Unionados, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Tu Patrono Tiene Su Union Pero Tu Patrono No Quiere Que Tu Tengas Tu Union: Por Que Actua Asi Tu Patrono?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Aumento de Salarios Para Trabajadores de la Industria del Sueter, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: La Abre la Concha del Explotador Del Trabajador Boricua, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: el plan medico ILGWU: HechosRealidades, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Plan Medico De La ILGWU, Locales 600-601, Puerto Rico Creando Mas Salud y Bienestar Para Mas Puertorriquenos, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Nosotros Somos La Union, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Otro Dispensario Medico, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: La ILGWU No Es Un Show, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: La Aguja, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: La Aguja, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    September 1971. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 16: La Aguja, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    October 1972. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 17: Este es el Plan Medico de la ILGWU, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Vota Para Lograr Mayor Seguridad, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Justicia, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    April 1972. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 20: Justicia, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    May 1972. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 21: Poster, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    By Clifford W. Depin. Item is in Spanish.
- ILGWU Notices, News clippings, 1928-1934; Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Cloakmakers of the Industrial Council Shops, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Cloakmakers! Vote for Week Work!, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Bulletin No. 1: The Season is On!, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Are You One of the Girls Who Says:, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: What Do You Get For Christmas?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: What Unions Do For The Community, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    By William Green. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: To all Workers of the Underwear Industry: Read! Think! Act!, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Signs Union Agreement, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    By E.Z. Mills. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Testimonial, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Title in Yiddish, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: Letter with Questions, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    October 16, 1928. Item is in English.
- Communists in Control, 1927; Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Communists in Control, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
    By Edward Levinson. Item is in English.
- New York Supreme Court, 1936; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Decision Rendered by Judge McCook on December 30th, 1936, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By L. Teper. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Plaintiff's Trial Memorandum, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By L.Teper. Item is in English.
- Schulman, Milton. Short History of the Dress and Waist Pressers', Local 60, ILGWU, 1943; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  May 1943
  - Item 1: Short History of the Dress and Waist Pressers', Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Milton Schulman. May 1943. Item is in English.
- Carriers' Exhibits, 1950-1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Conductors' and Trainmen's 40-Hour Week and Rules Case, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: The Nonoperating Employees' Fringe Benefits and Rules Case, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Dept., Survey of ILGWU, Shops engaged on Government Work: Jan.-Aug., 1951; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Survey of I.L.G.W.U. Shops Engaged On Government Work, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
- ILGWU - Social Security pamphlets, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: How Lucky Is My Social Security Number?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Social Security after 65, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Agreement between the Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc. and the ILGWU, 1930-1931; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between the Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc. And the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    February 12, 1930 - December 31, 1931. Item is in English.
- The Catholic World, 1959; Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  August 1959
  - Item 1: The Catholic World: What Eight Labor Leaders Believe, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
    August 1959. Item is in English.
- ILGWU, Report on ILGWU firms that have government contracts for uniforms, 1942; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Report on I.L.G.W.U. firms that have government contracts for uniforms, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Survey of Cloak Shops, 1924; Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Accounts Report: L.K.S. Cloak Co., Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    By Louis Lapidus. August 18, 1924. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Accountants Report: Sam Leopldstadt and Jacob Bernstein, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    By Louis Lapidus. August 19, 1924. Item is in English.